=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 23=
Tomorrow, at our wedding,
you will mix your blood
into this wine.
Blend it with mine.
Drinking this union cup
and our demonic marriage will be sealed.
This wine
is exquisite.
How can this be?
You drank it.
The deadliest poison
across the three realms?
Clever.
But you only found two of the three.
You almost killed me.
What a shame.
Impossible.
We gathered all three.
How could it be only two?
Master.
Lanxi.
It's you.
Why?
She is just a puppet,
something to watch you with.
Did you really think
she had an Underworld Soul?
Ridiculous.
Kill her.
Lanxi.
I knew you were fake.
I just wanted
to stay with you a little longer.
Even for a moment.
But
we finally found each other again.
We were one step from happiness.
Why?
Why can't I have
even the smallest bit of happiness?
Kill her.
Lanxi.
Ziyan.
You dare defy me for her?
Ah!
Ziyan.
Lanxi.
Lanxi!
I'll kill you!
Why?
Two halves of the same Stone
repel each other.
That's why you could never touch me.
So you knew all along
that I'm the Stone too.
But knowing won't help you.
I will still
devour you
bit by bit.
Ah!
(Yuanchu!)
Yuanchu.
♪Flowers bloom in turn,
as day and night trade places♪
♪Tides rise and fall.
Who watches fate unfold?♪
♪Beneath the boundless sky,
I turn toward the break of dawn♪
♪Alone in this world,♪
♪Searching for the traces
buried in my heart.♪
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
Who are you?
Heaven's Return Art.
Focus your spirit.
♪Do not forget the tangled paths♪
♪That you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
Is it pretty?
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪
Yuanchu.
(When our minds clashed earlier,)
(it wiped my memory.)
(By a twist of fortune,)
(my memories have all come back.)
Yuanchu,
I remember everything now.
I remember everything.
Your Love Flower bloomed because of him?
How absurd.
Then I'll kill him first.
And then devour you.
Mother!
My child.
Listen to me.
Run.
Stop fighting him.
You can't win.
Mother,
I am sorry.
I am truly sorry, mother.
This time, I can't run.
I don't want you to die.
I don't want you to die!
Mother.
Mother!
How is that human better than me?
The world, all beings, they're all mine.
What more do you want?
Love can't be forced,
nor can it be earned through effort.
Love is about giving,
not taking.
Do you understand?
If you won't love me,
then so be it.
In that case,
I will destroy you piece by piece.
Why?
Her Love Flower has bloomed.
Why can't I still touch the Stone?
Why?
It is impossible!
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away♪
♪This heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪